export const MOST_FAQS =  [
    {
      id: "faq-1",
      question: "Who is Herald Lenders ?",
      answer:
        "Herald Lenders  is a provider of unsecured personal loans for consumers serving FICO® scores up to 850. Through proprietary technology and algorithms, we’re driving a better lending and borrowing experience by finding more reasons to say “yes.” After serving hundreds of thousands of consumers, we’ve expanded into small business, and merchant point-of-sale lending solutions to further unlock access to affordable loans.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-2",
      question:
        "How does Herald Lenders  keep my personal and bank information safe?",
      answer:
        "Herald Lenders  takes extensive precautions to protect your personal information. We use robust industry-leading procedures and safeguards, including encryption, to secure and protect your personal information.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-3",
      question: "Does applying impact my credit score?",
      answer:
        "Providing your basic information to view loan options does not impact your credit score. To determine how much you could qualify for, we conduct a “soft pull” of your credit. If you select a loan option and continue your application, we require a “hard inquiry” to verify the information you’ve provided on the application for final loan approval. This “hard inquiry” will be seen as an inquiry on your credit report.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-4",
      question: "What is the eligibility criteria for a Herald Lenders loan?",
      answer:
        "To be eligible for a Herald Lenders loan, you must: \nBe 18 years or older \nBe able to provide a  state, or local government-issued photo ID \nHave a Social Insurance Number (SIN) \nHave a minimum annual income of $12,000 (from employment, retirement, or some other source) \nHave a verifiable personal banking account in your name",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-5",
      question: "How much can I borrow?",
      answer:
        "Our personal loans range from $1,000 to $50,000. The loan amount you may be approved for depends upon your individual credit profile and the information you provide during the application process. The maximum loan amount offered is based upon what is believed to be affordable for you. We take several factors into consideration including your current DTI (debt-to-income ratio) and PTI (payment-to-income ratio).",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-6",
      question: "Why was my application declined?",
      answer:
        "If your application was turned down, you’ll receive an email regarding the decision, including how to get a statement of specific reasons.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-7",
      question: "What’s the status of my loan application?",
      answer:
        "If we request additional documentation to complete your application, you’ll be notified of a decision within one to three business days once the information is received. You can check the status of your application by calling Customer Support Click Here ( link it to About us page )",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-8",
      question: "Why is my credit score important?",
      answer:
        "At Herald Lenders , we believe you are more than your credit score. Our model, using data and technology, looks beyond your credit score to allow us to see a more complete picture of you and your true credit worthiness.",
    },
  ];

  export const ALL_FAQS = [
    {
      id: "faq-1",
      question: "Who is Herald Lenders?",
      answer:
        "Herald Lenders is a provider of unsecured personal loans for consumers serving FICO® scores up to 850. Through proprietary technology and algorithms, we’re driving a better lending and borrowing experience by finding more reasons to say “yes.” After serving hundreds of thousands of consumers, we’ve expanded into small business, and merchant point-of-sale lending solutions to further unlock access to affordable loans.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-2",
      question: "What are your Privacy & Security Policies?",
      answer:
        "To review our privacy and security policies, please visit: www.Heraldlenders.com/privacy-notice",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-3",
      question: "How does Herald Lenders keep my personal and bank information safe?",
      answer:
        "Herald Lenders takes extensive precautions to protect your personal information. We use robust industry-leading procedures and safeguards, including encryption, to secure and protect your personal information.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-4",
      question: "Why is my credit score important?",
      answer:
        "According to Investopedia.com, a credit score is a number between 300–850 that depicts a consumer’s credit worthiness. The higher the score, the better a borrower looks to potential lenders. Many lenders, insurance companies, and other institutions use your credit score in making loan, credit, insurance, and even employment decisions.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-5",
      question: "What states are Herald Lenders loans offered in?",
      answer:
        "We offer loans to consumers in all provinces & territories of Canada.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-6",
      question: "Does applying impact my credit score?",
      answer:
        "Providing your basic information to view loan options does not impact your credit score. To determine how much you could qualify for, we conduct a “soft pull” of your credit. If you select a loan option and continue your application, we require a “hard inquiry” to verify the information you’ve provided on the application for final loan approval. This “hard inquiry” will be seen as an inquiry on your credit report.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-7",
      question: "Do you offer joint or cosigned loans?",
      answer:
        "At this time, Herald Lenders does not offer joint or cosigned loans. We offer personal loans based on an individual credit profile, taking into account only the applicant’s information and income (not joint or household).",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-8",
      question: "What is the eligibility criteria for a Herald Lenders loan?",
      answer:
        "To be eligible for a Herald Lenders loan, you must: \nBe 18 years or older \nBe able to provide a state, or local government-issued photo ID \nHave a Social Insurance Number (SIN) \nHave a minimum annual income of $12,000 (from employment, retirement, or some other source) \nHave a verifiable personal banking account in your name",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-9",
      question: "What documents may be required for approval?",
      answer:
        "During the approval process, we may require a few documents to verify the information you provided on your application. Requested documents may include a driver’s license, pay stub(s), bank statements, or employment verification.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-10",
      question: "What is the loan process?",
      answer:
        "Our goal is to make the loan process as easy as possible. Simply apply online or call and speak to one of our loan specialists. You’ll select the loan option that works best for you, set up your repayment preferences, then sign your loan agreement. You may be asked to upload a few documents to help verify your application information. Once we receive a complete application, we provide a decision as soon as possible.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-11",
      question: "How long does it take for my loan to be approved?",
      answer:
        "Based on your credit profile and the information provided on the application, Herald Lenders returns your loan offer(s) in just seconds. Once you have selected your preferred loan option, we’ll ask for some additional information. In some cases, you may be asked to provide some additional documentation to help verify information on your application. Once any additional documentation is received and reviewed a final loan approval is completed.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-12",
      question: "What’s the status of my loan application?",
      answer:
        "If we request additional documentation to complete your application, you’ll be notified of a decision within one to three business days once the information is received. You can check the status of your application by calling Customer Support.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-13",
      question: "Why was my application declined?",
      answer:
        "If your application was turned down, you’ll receive an email regarding the decision, including how to get a statement of specific reasons.",
    },
    {
      id: "faq-14",
      question: "How much can I borrow?",
      answer:
        "Our personal loans range from $1,000 to $50,000. The loan amount you may be approved for depends upon your individual credit profile and the information you provide during the application process. The maximum loan amount offered is based upon what is believed to be affordable for you. We take several factors into consideration including your current DTI (debt-to-income ratio) and PTI (payment-to-income ratio).",
    }
];
